Jesús Simeone Ambrocio Hernández

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Age: 24 years Nationality: Mexican

Languages: Spanish, English

SKILLS

- Software engineering
- C++, C# and Python
- Unreal Engine and Unity
- · Tools generation
- DirectX 11 and OpenGL

CONTACT



Guadalajara, Jalisco, México



443 127 66 69



simamb@outlook.com



@Sime0647_Boo



linkedin.com/in/simeboo/

C++/Gameplay Programmer/Engine Programmer

Experience in creation and development of custom videogame engines, teamwork, Unreal Engine and Unity, computer graphics and documentation. Always work with good communication, flexibility, dedication and attention to detail. Like to take the initiative to help companions.

EDUCATION

Videogame Development Engineering Digital Arts University, Guadalajara, Jalisco, México August 2019 - December 2022

Career focused in the process of videogame development, commercial videogame engines usage and generation of tools for videogames in C++.

EXPERIENCE

Carbon Machina [March 2023 - Present]

Unreal Engine

Implementation of a Minecraft-like crafting system and helped to develop the studio inner framework abstracting and generalizing classes allowing a better workflow for everyone on the team.

Unity

Development of all game user interface, audio system and implementation, character customization system and general programming for an unannounced boxing-like RPG game.

Attribute Overload [March 2023 - Present]

Unreal Engine

Frontend development of a tool that allows audio loading and actor instantiation. The actors follow user-given points placed in the audio timeline through all the playback time.

Inner Engine

Development of the rendering, UI and colaboration modules of a custom videogame engine.

Capture and generation of hyperspectral images simulator (Independent)

School research project presented in the following conferences:

- National Congress of Space Activities (CONACES)(September 2022, Aguascalientes, México).
- XX International Symposium of the Latin American Society for Remote Sensing and Spatial Information Systems (SELPER) (October 2022, Monterrey, Nuevo León, México)

Implementation in Unreal Engine of the real-time image capture and export system and its transcription [Publication in process] (May 2021 - December 2022).

Boo Engine (Independent) [September 2021 - Present]

Development of own custom videogame engine from scratch which includes a math library, engine's core, 3D model loading, actor-component system and actor instantiation, renderer and graphics modules and a connection with the colaboration software NVIDIA Omniverse. https://youtu.be/4jd2eb8WBSY